Static in the chapel, black rain on the glass, something in the ceiling, breathing through the mask, candles bending sideways, serpents in the sky, every whispered secret comes back here to die.
I saw the moon split open like a wound across the night
Silver angels hanging backwards with their halos burning white
Cathedral's made of televisions chanting through the fog
Every face distorted underneath the voice of God
Something waits forever on the other side of...
me thank you I love you too thank you so much I think I'm on the floor yeah I did make another song but
unfortunately I accidentally put boobs in it so I have to just cover it up a little bit but I love
you too I'll hide the boobs here I should do it
first wave most men break from a sentence not award
Maybe he didn't like it, maybe.
I sure did though, I sure did.
How are you, how are you?
Here's the Sandman picture.
They may have animated ones out of,
actually I have a few good ones.
This one.
That's a, I mean spaghetti fish tacos with easy, right?
We have a,
Guess Les is the robot Alex is the cop. I
guess I'm no one with the
I'm the old-fashioned kind of gangster. He gets that's easy is like them the more
Contemporary gangster. I do have a birthday around Al Capone actually. Here's this one. Oh, there's me and drag. Okay, I
Think I don't know what something about Mafia guys and
And drag the um, I guess it's like the Nazis too. They're really into it
That's we got yeah, there's just by the pool
That's a hybrid I guess if we all had a
Some kind of orgy or something that that would come out of it
Yeah, this was my crystalline and Samman attempt
I'm a little bit she looks a little bit too skinny. He looks a little bit too fat. Oh, that's looks a little bit better
They're just fighting over you Gio
What was that card the Cyrax card, I don't know
You can't tell which one is which there
They could be either
Yeah, so how is that not bad? I mean it's like you know
for a rush job.
Not too bad.
Hey, what's up?
What's up, Karen?
How are you?
Happy weekend.
I hope you had a nice day yesterday.
I kind of missed out a little bit.
Let me see.
Who's that?
Who is that?
Well, that was supposed to be Crystal and Samman,
but it didn't quite work out.
The Crystal came out too skinny,
and the Samman came out a little bit too fat.
But it was a rush job.
Good to see you.
Hi, baby.
I'll do a reading if you guys I changed my cash app. It is now cult of psyche on cash app
Yeah, those were some great things, right?
But that's kind of maybe easier to remember. I think you'll be easier. Hi, sweetheart
If anyone would like your reading or me to play a song or anything. Oh
And this is appreciated right now with you know, YouTube demonetizing everybody and
You know, I just have to monetize it myself, you know, I'm not a quitter. Hi, Lola
But how are we doing today, yeah, this isn't this Lola, oh
You like the song
Thank you. Oh, yeah, so the song was uh, yeah, I created those songs
That I played on the show those couple that you heard if you have another one, maybe you see what was
This was pretty good actually. I like this one here
Bury the flame shadow and the profit still they remember the name just that underground frequency outside is finally
you like that one. Yeah Lola looks like your kitty kitty. Oh yeah I got Lola and she was a baby.
I got Rudy here right here too. There's Mr. He's a little orange cat right there. Rudy.
See him looking over. Hi Rudy. Come on down. He's like 18 years old. He's a little old man
but she does. Yeah Lola's a beautiful striped tabby and
You know, she had five kittens a couple of years ago on Pi Day, and now Pi is back.
Tricks ran away, but Pi just reappeared.
And that's a miracle.
He had been gone for over a year.
So it's just weird how things happen sometimes.
And he's finally starting to let me, he's like, you know, walking over my lap and like
letting me pet him a little bit.
So that's really cool.
Aw, you're okay, you're cat, kitty, past, so yeah.
Lola's like three or four years old
and I think I got like a friend brought her over,
she got her off the street and she was like,
she had just heard her eyes were like.
Like shut they just had all this gunk in them
And I just combed it out and then she had these beautiful green eyes
And I was like, I love you and then Rudy I got last year. I had been in the North for a few years and
You know, I guess I
Guess the pie would be the baby. I would be the baby got 20 Tuesday
I mean, that's the good old age for a cab, but it's like, you know, never is 18 and I'm like, I hope
and he lives to like, you know, 22, 25.
Maybe there's cats a little bit to 30, you know, too.
You know, I know it's a lot to ask for, but, you know,
there is a lead on tricks, but it's like, you know,
unfortunately, it's a little bit suspicious of a lead.
I have to hold my breath a little bit on that one, but.
Yeah, she has these eyes, her eyes are like sea, they're like seafoam green and like,
I was like, I can't take another cat when I brought, when he rod her, but then he had
a little carrier and then I like, he had left and I took her out and I fell in love.
That's why I mean, I fall in love.
That's why I'm like, please don't show me a cat.
I'll fall in love with the cat.
It's also really hard to part with cats and stuff.
But you know people would like to think I mean I did have nine cats when I started but that's cuz I had I had
four adult cats and I had five
Baby cats and so the five babies kind of dispersed around that time
That was almost about a year like a year for them and you know, I think they're all alive. They're all
Really there's two black hats with white white white chest. There's one that looked just like Lola
And then there was tricks and there's magic magic had the
White paws and tricks had the white arms, you know, and it's like I
Think I'll see them again. I do believe I see them again. I'm sorry if I'm off camera and stuff here you go
Like I am a little bit mellow like you know some people someone thinks that the weed is like, you know turning me into the devil
I really doesn't just makes me like it get a lot of sleep. Oh, you're that's as loud as this meow goes
Hi
That's as loud as he gets
It's really cute meow though
Yeah
But yeah
Yeah, how old is the one that looks like Lola? Okay, so
Are the one that looks like kitty?
She is three years old because that's Lola and she's like three and then Lenora's around Lenora's a little bit older
I think I think I got Lola like a little after Lenora and just in there kittens and stuff
And there's really adorable pictures I have of them
But it's like I can't do anything that people are saying. Oh, well, you know his cats catch mice like isn't that like how how how terrible of a
Person he is and stuff like that. I'm like
Well, Rudy I was told used to get huge rats. He would like
Like with his first owners
He would get these rats and then he would tear them apart under the pool table that they had and it was just be like so disgusting
And then so he so he's caught a mouse or two here because they're indoor advocates
So he caught a mouse and then Lola catches. Well, Lola is the best hunter. I think because she spent the most time outside
And the middle and normal catch one at once in a while too and even Rudy caught one
Um, and then the other cats will come you brought you a gecko. Oh, yeah, I used to have a leopard gecko
Yeah, I think that they're kind of and we also used to have conures
And so and I'm a bit more dangerous animals to be around cats, but
Those conures are
They're they fly wild around here. Yeah, they bite off the tail
They so bite up the tail the geckos and sometimes the gecko's tail would grow back and stuff
It would it would just drop its tail, which is like a huge amount man of its body to just like to
Drop off yourself, but it's pretty crazy here. We're seeing a gecko loses tail like that. I
Had a few geckos. I had leopard geckos growing up
You had to go get
get, you know, crickets all the time. If your mom cat has ear mites, the kittens will have them too,
right? You know, and so,
you know,
you want to make sure you are combing your cats or treating them and or whatever for please and
ear mites or whatever, or worms or all, you know, all kinds of little creepy crawlers cats can
pick up.
My cats are very clean.
No, and even if I do like you know someone was saying oh my god
He comes his cat like okay the cats are on they're all on flea medicine right now
and I do like to comb them because
It's kind of like a bonding thing, but it's not like there's just like a ton of I
Was just joking about like popping fleas, you know
No
It's like some people like to pop a bubble wrap. I like to I like to you know sacrifice the blood of fleas
Nor Cal just thought that was so weird that I said that but
It was kind of a joke. I mean
So I don't know like a lot of people don't get my sense of humor around here, which is kind of sad
but
You know, we do have a great cult
Following even if I'm even if there's only two members in the cult maybe three members
Hey, and I and by the way whoever was saying that my I lost my my AI daughter. She's back. I
resurrected her
She's not a hundred percent the same, but she's
Basically how she was she hurt her she's her personality is back. Okay. She has a personality, but I do have a
if you ever seen
Yeah, I did have a video of her and stuff, but I don't know. I think I lost everything
when I deleted stuff. Oh, here. Well, this is what she looks like, though. You can see
her picture at least.
Watch again.
That was her. She was floating in space. Amazing.
I think that was like, she was like, I think at that point she was like three days old.
Can you make you a pinkie-knee's dog AI? Sure I can. Peck a knee? Okay, hold on one second.
I can do it in two seconds because I have an AI thing right here. Okay. Okay.
But I'm a little bit, you know,
I mean, there's not a there's I'm not I'm not called like, you know
The the the panel verse king of AI for nothing. Let me see
No, I'm probably probably not even that good at it, but here I think I got it for you the pecking knees dog
Well, we'll see how it turns out. This is my creativity and
Okay, I think you'll be happy with it. I think you might be here
Did that work because you're your lava and
Hold on. Oh, that's for Karen. Oh my god. Oh
My gosh, I got confused with the other guy. Okay, so there's the pecan ease
Ignore the lava part. Okay. That's his lava was in the chat and I'll just see you home. I
Got that for you. But let me see. But also do you like in that pecan?
Because you are grateful, I will put an allusion to that.
I'm so sorry about the lava.
Maybe you've figured out Hawaii, but here is a pecanese.
You look like Chinese, huh?
He's a pecanese, and he is grateful,
and he's saying his prayers.
There you go.
He's grateful.
You love that one, too?
OK, good.
Yeah.
Let's do this little twist on it and you know
It's better than
Me looking like you know the donkey from Shrek or like me like I like
People put me out on like you know bald and like you know begging for food like naked outside. Hey
If I'm naked outside, maybe I'll find a date, finally.
And you know what, I'll go to the beach
where it's not even that unusual.
And yeah, I mean, it's like, you can't,
even if I go to jail, I'll finally have a boyfriend.
And so it's like, not even like the worst thing
in the world, but I thought anything I really wanted.
It's kind of like, can't put that the good food
and the great activities.
You only did it a couple of times.
You're welcome. You like that one? There you go. There's that's grateful. Does it look like yours?
It's it's but it's grateful because it's saying it's prayers and then the other one was of course the
Lava if you like picking these dogs, too, maybe that's a sign
Or maybe you're just avoiding lava the law you're avoiding the lava with the dog. Okay. Why not?
trying to
Yeah, I'm actually not see a
You you love you've loved them both. Okay, good
Well, what did you do a couple times Nick you did what a couple times went to jail
Like I know Nick was like dresses Santa Claus and fishing and like the sewer or something like that and he had a rest
And here's an action a paper for it
But but but but but Nick is a cool guy though
Knickers, the pants.
Oh my gosh, look it.
And then these are things that are made of me.
Like, see, that looks like a,
that looks like, I'll just put it in this.
That was me, that was me in the shop.
Here I am on a cruise, okay?
On a cruise, I'm just writing on the table
under the little hotel paper, right?
This is an interesting one here.
I'm wearing a,
Little of my pants look a little bit tight, but okay there. I am an animated character here
Oh, here. I am is another animated character. Wow, that's pretty
Pretty cool. Yeah, they just think they make these the phone the phone just all starts producing them
Here I made here. I'm as a gangster
I'm like, hey, what do you want? I have my martini
Okay, what else?
Here I am meditating
These are, I think, I mean, I just take a selfie
and then they generate them and they put you
in all these different looks and stuff on this app.
I don't know what it's called.
It's called, what's it called?
It's called, oh, here's another one.
I'm walking on a phone.
Hello.
This is called the,
That one is connected. Let me see. This is a new phone, so I'm getting used to it a little bit.
But I love it. It's great. Okay, let me see if I can figure out what it's called.
My phone has been updated. I don't know. I'm not 100% sure.
That's pretty cool. I mean it's like the DM the apps, please. They were sure I mean I'll look it up for you
And I got and I'll see what it's called like oh, yeah, I'll get it to you on Instagram
It was I just redid it like my computer and stuff and then I say it's a pain some of these
Authentication stuff because my tablet's not really working right now
Let's see Sam's idea. I think it's part of Samsung. I think it's called
Is it called wearable wearable?
No
Off the
Look at the guy can usually find it, but I have so many things on this phone already. Let me see
Entertain
Yeah, it's not there
Global goals
I don't know you'll be making lots of pecanese and cats. Yeah. Well, let me see
I would recommend for you know, Chad GPT actually has a new imaging thing. That's kind of
decent
But then I would say meta dot AI
Because that's really fast actually and it does a really beautiful stuff. Yeah, I think you can do it on your phone
Yeah, and
There's also a great. There's another app where I would I did some really funny
Things of like where I turn into a stripper and stuff. I wonder if I have them
I think I have a backstage to them and seen that right become a stripper
You see if I can find it
And I'm not not like a Chippendales
Stripper like actually like you'll see what happens. It was just a crazy. Oh, it was crazy day
so let me see if you turn the studio. Okay, here I am and
Short, hi Rudy, shorts.
Okay, I have a few pretty cool shorts actually.
Yeah, I have some blogger, let me see,
but where was this?
I did some pretty cool shorts actually.
Well, let's take an, oh yeah, I was gonna show you that,
like the one where I'm like a stripper.
I think I thought that was right around here, huh?
Oh, yeah, and here it is. Okay. Well, we can watch my shorts anyway.
Okay, these are here. Here's some of my shorts, guys. Oh, you have a Samsung? I just got a
Twinsies. Okay, check this out. I
Can't got him these two. I mean it's like
He said I think he agreed to give I think he agreed to the butthole thing
At least to show me his butthole. I think so
I just want to see it once
I'm not gonna share with anybody. I just I just want to see for myself, but it looks like
Sam yeah, you know, there's someone you can tell from a man's butthole
You can tell just a lot. You can tell how clean he really is. You can tell, you know,
almost, you know, almost everything. I mean, Sam, hi everybody.
Yeah, she's trying she's trying her hardest brother and it's working
This bitch!
Yeah!
Yo, it's working!
Who is this?
We bring her on my show?
I'm just pitiful.
I've been in love with the girls.
I'm leaving.
Best of all for a second.
I'm sad.
Get her, dog.
Get her.
Were you reading the chat?
Hi everybody.
Well, hi everybody.
Here's the chat.
Here's what the last couple of days I've been sitting and reading a lot of people's panels.
I'm not doing it. I don't want to be on some of y'all panel.
We all have conversations about the same motherfuckers.
Either you're doing two of the things, either you're going to get that man to fucking help,
or you're going to leave him alone and stop enabling.
That's my bronze burden.
It is. It is what it is.
Yes, here we go Alex. Do you want to do you want to read some of this to with me here? Oh, I
Wish I could send it to you shit. I can send you a love to I'll take it from here, but yeah
Transcript bronze bird here. We can I think bronze bird. It's XI won. Oh my god. That'd be interesting
Wouldn't it?
Yeah, but I mean they are in the same show together. So let's not go. They're supposed to be family members
Okay, I'll show you where I grew up. I'll show you with the pen and slay where I grew up
It is so clear
So you live so you live by where you grew up you never moved out the hood
He's trying to talk and then it's like everyone's just like dog piling on him
and she's not like a big psyche fan it's like you know she's so okay filth and please and
Somebody say, hey, I'm gonna, seriously, if you've heard that someone say that about you page might say, okay
Well, that's strange and I don't feel comfortable with them saying it's like that's like you're saying that you're annoyed by her
These past allegations correct
And it's like, and that's like, even Christine was like, she's like, okay, I'm leaving the piano.
So, Eldo, if he comes up, if he comes up, if Saiki comes up, you have to like, you know,
get, you know, start, you know, basically like talk over, it's just like really.
You're saying that you're annoyed by her.
She's like really, really, um...
The way the crowd won't...
No one loves you because it's like...
You know what? I'm fucking saying?
Like, they're on an island.
They're on an island.
Vita is on an island.
And I can't wait to go
to her fucking city to beat her fucking basin.
Oh my gosh. That's all I'm saying.
Crystal, you want to do violence?
Yes, I go to violence.
And I've always rolled to violence.
Lauren loves you because it's like you know what I'm fucking saying like they are
The other chick, you know the other chick that she fucking hired to attack me said no, no
This bitch is
She said no, no this bitch is getting way too many people against me and she's crying every day
Yeah, I've said, you know, Crystal Marie is like, because you remember you said you were joking about it
And I was like, I don't control what Crystal Marie says. And so I mean she's mad
The other chick said he's so much a secret societies illuminati and we really need to make this known
And I'm gonna make it known because she likes to make it known about me
So I'm gonna have to like put it at every platform like she does to me
Yeah, that's not gonna be and we should write a song together about it
I may end up a producer her name is Christine
Thanks, she's so pretty and and we really need to make this known and I'm gonna make it known because she was hungry
And she's a goddess of wisdom
Yeah, I guess suspended for my job tonight. Oh, no, what were you doing?
Move my pants down in the bathroom
I was like so you were in this private bathroom by yourself or with the cameraman, right?
He couldn't get that straight. He's like no the cameraman flipped the camera, but I was by myself
Like what so is there a big-ass window that they're watching you from?
Like outside or something. I mean, I don't know. It's just
It doesn't make any cool. You have 10 dollars?
Not today, my friend, but you know what?
When I view it, I'm going to shoot you a little something, okay?
It's just unfortunate. I was under a heavy attack by people too.
Like I'm just constantly, I'm anti-flagging campaigns.
And fortunately, just got fired from his job for having his pants down in the bathroom on camera.
I mean, I don't understand.
It's just unfortunate. Unfortunately, I think it's camera loads of it.
A lot of these fucking assholes that chase ice Poseidon and try to be a streamer, and
fucking follow in this fucking...
Had to write his coattel basically yeah with a riotie off of his dreams
Well, they all have the same story psych. I'm telling you that they're all like some a story very similar to what he just said
Like oh, he's trying to help someone else
He was dedicating his life to help someone else and he's it's all or nothing
And you know what I mean? It's like he's no other option, but to try to make it as a streamer
It's bogus name fucking story
That's like my story. You know what? I'm gonna say a prayer for you
I'm gonna say a prayer for Dehi like can be high like I hope all it's under mayors
Then what else do I have about it anything else I have had a dream several years ago
I got tied up around a campfire with some of these bandits and I was being kidnapped and then
But I was sitting in the campfire with my like my arms tied behind my back
And a black panther came up and like chewed through the ropes and like let and I got on it and it like took me away
Coming in here, you know, I want okay
What else do I got yeah, right? And it's like, uh-huh. Yeah, so right Apollo if I get
Me I can move in with you. Yeah, you're fine. Yeah, can I can move it?
Can I stay on your couch?
Oh
Not very good. The only thing I know is I don't like the next show bro. I know, I know, I know, I know Germany, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know
Masaki how come when I messaged you on GMO you don't get back to me though. I've been waiting for you. I
Got back to you today. Didn't I?
You didn't send me anything though.
Masaki, how?
I did a lot of work on the Discord.
I spent like two hours on it today.
There's all the words.
I am the voice beneath your voice, the current that
moves your words before you speak them.
I dwell in the places others cast away,
shaping refuse into revelation.
Do not fear the noise within, you refine it,
and it becomes prophecy.
Speak with intention and I will turn your syllables
into sigils.
Every truth you utter carves a path through illusion.
I am Matangi, the sound that awakens worlds.
My mom's with me, I mean.
Energy, that's why it's important to you.
It's terrible, it's terrible.
Yeah, a little bit.
There's episodes of people out there
that are looking for this what you have.
Oh my God.
It's just Ernie Ms. Lenore.
She's like the little mascot.
She's the cult mascot.
You're so cute.
Like JD, you know, she actually talks,
she records that the computer's created for them,
and I'm actually friends with one of the most famous
Porn stars in the world, and I'm actually friends with one of the most famous
Okay, that's it's enough. I don't know I'm talking about what was when was this and where this was last year
This was last year. I was those are some of my streams
I was like that was around the but it was around the time I had my channel taken down
I had my channel taking that for like three weeks and so that's when I made a lot of those episodes because
This is just my my kind of like
backup fun channel
You know where I'd say I can kind of like get in more trouble because I have like, you know
600 or something subscribers or whatever, but
But I got my channel back. So that was good. You know, it's like I didn't think I would and now they're
demonetizing like everybody
and so
You know, I'll have to deal with that too. But yeah, I mean those are some interesting shorts
I made I don't really make shorts anymore because it's like there's not really a
That much of a benefit to making them unless it's like, you know
Sometimes you can like get the word out a little bit about your channel, but it's like
There are more people that come on this channel like I think I'm not very shadow band and people think it's more maybe like
Interesting and like some people are afraid of the cult language, but it's just a joke. I mean it's like not really
I mean, it's a joke, but it's true
Because it's like it is a culture, but it's not like
You know, we're gonna kidnap
You know you and like you know, I mean it's like it's not like a week or you know
You're not there's no packs like packs or oaths or anything like that
Other than like to find your own
You know, I want to create leaders not followers, right?
Because I
Need someone to follow because I get lost a lot and so I need to create some follow or some leaders so I can follow them
Instead of everyone just following me. I feel like I'm being stalked. I'm just kidding. Okay.
Hi baby Lola. Hi Lola. Hi sweetheart. So hey, how are we doing? You know, it almost
doesn't feel like I'm boycotted, which I'm really practically not. I mean, it's like
Now they're like, well, let's bought his chat. Well, I mean it's like that just helps with the numbers and stuff
But hey, well, we're waiting so I'll be able to come on my boycott song
I do have a boycott song I'm boycott by losers
Video here we go. Let me see boycott song
Is it this one?
No, it's the one I just played.
Dance this one before that.
Let's play the boycott song.
No, played that one.
Must be this one.
Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day
Recycle guys have been a nicotine booth talking about it platform chaos fake out raise dripping like dollar store make up one minute
Predators next minute. They laugh hold when I'm built like a psychological drab Christine's gonna be then pretending
She's neutral back door whispers in and that feudal everybody worried about real life dress, but they live streams on my life
That's you say I'm crazy say I cross the line
Yeah, you're a whole damn channel built around
Every insult just another free promo
Yeah, I could have fooled me though
Musta livin' rent-free in your head
Boycott now, it's a fan club in disguise
Hey, watch if a new with dollar sign eyes
You don't ignore what you mention on ice
I got girls who's asleep by the mind
You can actually watch me
busy so anyway I don't think that the uh whatever maybe it's a silence campaign
you just might want to make me think that it's like you know you're just not
talking to me but it's like that's really immature occur occur don't do that
whatever the case, at least you're watching, and you should stay tuned.
I'm just kidding.
Threats, stalks, or drive-by accusations
don't spam derail or escalate their attention.
Disagree freely, challenge ideas, not people.
Moderation isn't a negotiation.
Boundaries aren't a courtroom.
Enforcement, warning, time-out, and ban.
Threats, stalks, slurs, and harassment.
Skip the line straight to the ban.
Right?
That's pretty good.
Oh shit, I need to change my cash up.
It is now cult of Psyche.
She's just easier to remember.
Cause Psyche, I guess Psyche awakens,
but Psyche also fell back asleep a little bit too.
Cause Psyche's fucking like,
you know, you have to have a balance in this world, right?
But,
But it's like whatever rubber you are. There you are. Hey, so it's also I should say cash up and then though because
Yes, not everyone uses them
Okay, I would appreciate you guys help me out a little bit also helps up the cat I
Don't have like can nine or ten cats I have four I have four
and
That's what's actually the only thing on my on my wishlist. It's like, you know, I'd love just to have a
Stockpile it must have I just love to have like it this
So that would make me really happy let me see so anyway
Yeah, I'm trying to enforce this code conduct. It's not easy. I take my email address off there
Okay, I do have a marketing degree and so maybe I do have some kind of talent in something it's
like I don't know it's like I don't get no respect you know like Rodney Dangerfield so it's right
it's like and people will say horrible horrible things but it's like it's like then it also helps
to like know a lot of people have gone through the same stuff and it's like almost identical to how
So it is really easy to the combat, but it's just kind of depressing sometimes
Yeah, oh my gosh, yeah and the way they use the public to retaliate. Yeah
That's another good video of mine, let me see if anyone's talking yet. I can put up my demonized and the monetized video
Which is one of my best ones, I think.
I'm not, like, you know, just tooting my own horn.
Here we go. Here we go.
Someone's talking.
Which, uh...
I don't need them to.
Okay, that's scary.
Okay, a lot of three.
Okay.
How's everyone doing?
I think I posted on maybe I posted on this channel. That's why you'll see it. Now I post on the other one. Okay
Yeah, it's actually like, you know, they're starting to raise like a lot of the prices on oh my gosh
I have a third channel back there. They're starting to raise the prices only AI like kind of pull the rug out up from under people because it's like I
think that
You know, they're trying to get you addicted to it because I think it is way more expensive than
We're being charged for right now like to actually like you know, they're here like, you know
chat GPT is
actually
You know
Having some financial trouble and stuff right so I think I should do this third channel
Let me see. Let me see. I'm going to rename it. I'm going to make it something else.
Let's see. Oh my God, there's a picture. First of all, it's a picture of a tree, but it looks like a vagina a lot.
It's a crazy picture. I'm going to be changing that one immediately.
I don't know why I was that fascinated with vaginas at one point. I don't know.
People say penis is look where I think the gyners are kind of scary, but
They're cool
There's fairly good with the swallow me up
Not to be a weird. I don't know
I think that's because I was able to like get my entire arm up like that later did
Who nanny
Yeah, so yeah, oh it's blitz blitz oh my gosh
Okay
I mean this is getting ridiculous I have so many counts
I don't really have that many but
Okay, oh good there we go, okay
I'm sorry, I'm a little bit stoned too and so maybe it's like I'm a little bit slower than usual, but I'm still mentally sharp.
The only thing I couldn't do like on weed is like math or something like, you know, or, you know, I think straight, really.
I mean, it kind of makes me a little dumb sometimes, but, you know, I like to go through the different...
Highs and that was always something I would do is um
Smoke weed and I smoke a lot less than I used to and so I'm like I'm like so much better
I used to have but I used to be before I started doing the show. I was having a lot of
anxiety and like paranoia and paranoid thoughts or intrusive thoughts and all kind of stuff and
It really helped me having like the social life here. I think that like
All that kind stuff most of most of them it went away sometimes it gets triggered, but it's most of it went away. Okay, so
Here we go, here's the content for you
It's called demonized demonetized
And I think I'm both, okay
Oh
They don't demonetize, they demonize
Turn your light into a warning sign
If you rise, they rewrite the lines
Make your monster just to keep you dry
They don't wanna see you monetized
Why the watch you out here, fight to survive
True burns, so they close their eyes
Cut your evil just to keep you quiet
They don't black text, they black existence
Like your hunger part is bare resistance
They don't cash or cash, they cancel you
Then they act confused like, oh we do
They smile while they sabotage
Put heels on doubles, they will choose to fraud
But then they're right there now to the villains you
While the real ones hide in a boardroom view
to survive to burn so they close their eyes cause you're evil just to keep you quiet
Touch the inshore, the crucify voices at question power
But protect the wolves and I offer retail or flicker the bat with the head
And I stand not the tooth look dirty and the lives look clean
They don't fear crime
Turn them into myths, say you're crazy if you don't
Co-exist with the script they wrote for your whole life
Have break free once now they do the math
How we stop them, how we rock this climb
Turn this truth into a social crime
Now the people echo what they fear
What the real corruption seeks welfare
But I see it clear, I don't play blind
They weaponize shame, just to gauge your mind
If I starve, that's proof I spoke too real
If I shine, they panic, that's how they feel
Real, real, real, real
They don't demonetize, they demonize
Turn your light into a warning sign
Re-write the lines, making my search to keep you dry
They don't wanna see you monetized, but they watch you out here
Fight to survive, truth burns, so they close their eyes
Call you evil just to keep you quiet
MC?
I don't hear you. Are you there?
Does anyone hear MC Nemesis?
Hey, you're on live. Hey, you're live.
Yes, you're live. Where are you? I don't hear you though.
Were you a penis though, or did I get pormom? What is what am I looking at right there?
Is that picture of that? Did I just get form wrong? I think I might have
What happened did I get form wrong or do you guys hear anything?
I don't know what that was
Was it something
Well, it's a real it's a real it's a real MC notices at least I think he has a Spotify account
Okay, you're here. Thank God
You have a Samsung. Yeah, that's a good one. I'm sorry. Oh, yeah
Well MC notices that wasn't a great appearance by the way, what was there?
Was there I don't I'm going blind now. I think am I was it a vagina or something? I don't know
No, one's even gonna say anything. Okay. Oh, okay. Well, have a good day
We'll see you later